Center for International Education and Global Strategy; Records ua550
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Center for International Education and Global Strategy Records
1941 - 2017 May 17
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
ua550
19.36 cubic ft.
28 captures
The collection consists of inactive records from the University at Albany's Center for International Education and Global Strategy and its predecessor offices.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
All items in this collection were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Arrangement
The Collection is organized into five different series. The first series is made up of files related to the management of Overseas Academic Programs (OAPs), the official name at the time for study abroad programs that the University administered. The second series is made up of administrative records of the Office itself. The third series is made up of the Office's letter files and informational binders the office kept on their overseas programs. The fourth series is made up of Articulation Agreements with overseas universities. The final series is made up of webcrawls of the Office's website.
Administrative History
The University at Albany's Office of International Programs was established in 1964 as the Office of International Studies and World Affairs. In 1971, it became the Office of International Programs. At that time, Former Associate Dean of Arts and Sciences Charles W. Colman became the Director of International Programs. Colman held this position formally until his retirement 1980. He remained in the position as Acting Director until at least 1985. The Office was renamed the Office of International Education before becoming the Center for International Education and Global Strategy in 2015.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Web Archives
Scope and Contents
This collections consists of inactive records of University at Albany's Office of International Programs as well as web archives of its successors the Office of International Education and the Center for International Education and Global Strategy. Many of the files in this collection appear to come from the office of Charles W. Colman, the Director of International Programs during much of the period covered. This collection includes: correspondence, budgets and financial statements, program proposals and site visit reports, student program evaluations, program brochures and reference binders on the various programs retained by the Office. Materials in this collection document a number of overseas academic programs and summer language programs including those based in Nice, France; Wurzburg, Germany Tel Aviv and Haifa, Israel; Rome, Italy; Curenavaca and Guadalajara, Mexico; Moscow, Russia; Coimbra, Portugal; Singapore; and Madrid, Spain.
Web Archives; UAlbany Academic Administration; Wages -- New York (State); Correspondence.; Foreign study; State University of New York at Albany-Office of International Programs
- Overseas Academic Programs, 1965-1980; 10 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Series is arranged in its original order. Files appear to have been generally organized alphabetically by the location of the program.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the files related to the management of individual overseas academic programs (OAPs) of varying length, from year-long and semester length to summer programs for both current SUNY Albany students and entering freshmen. Contains budget documentation, student activity reports, student program evaluations, Director's correspondence, brochures and informational packets given to students, travel itineraries, planning documentation, program proposals, and site visit reports for potential program locations.
  - African Studies Faculty Association, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Asian Area Studies, 1970-1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Asia Foundation, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Directors Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cuernavaca, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Cuernavaca Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Cuernavaca Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Cuernavaca Directors Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - CIDOC, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - CIDOC-CALE, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Cuernavaca Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Cuernavaca Participants, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cuernavaca Participants, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Cuernavaca, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Freshmen Summer Language Summers, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cuernavaca Program, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cuernavaca Program, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - FSLP Canada Financial, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Coimbra, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - FSLP Canada, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - FSLP Brochure, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - FSLP Budget, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - FSLP Committee, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - FSLP Committee, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - FSLP Correspondence, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - FSLP Cuernavaca, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - FSLP EOP Financial, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - FSLP France, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - FSLP France, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - FSLP France Directors Correspondence, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - FSLP France Directors Correspondence, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - FSLP Evaluations, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - CAEN FSLP Program in France, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - France Lists, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - FSLP Germany, 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - FSLP General Information, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - FSLP General, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - FSLP General, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - FSLP Germany, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - FSLP Germany, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - FSLP Israel, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - FSLP Germany, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Lists Germany, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - FSLP Grading, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - FSLP Italy, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - FSLP Italy, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - FSLP Italy, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Italy Lists Summer, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - FSLP Itineraries, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - FSLP, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - FSLP Land Transportation, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - IG2F Linczenyi, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - FSLP List of Participants, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - FSLP Planning Program, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Planning, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Universite De Caen Brochures, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - FSLP Perugia, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - FSLP Planning, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Munro Clair Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - FSLP Portugal, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Portugal Lists, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Portugal Site Description, Undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Publicity FSLP, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - FSLP Puerto Rico, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - FSLP Puerto Rico, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - FSLP Report, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - FSLP Report, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - FSLP Registration, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - FSLP Registration, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - FSLP Russia, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - FSLP Russia, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - FSLP Spain, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - FSLP Spain, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - FSLP Spain Directors reports, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - FSLP Spain Directors Correspondence, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - FSLP Spain Directors Correspondence, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - FSLP Spain, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Fulbright Regional Conference, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Fulbright Regional Conference, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Guadalajara, 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Guadalajara Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Guadalajara Director's Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Guadalajara Director's Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Guadalajara, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Guadalajara Participants, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Guadalajara Participants, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Guadalajara Program, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Guadalajara Program List, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Guadalajara Program, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Guadalajara Program, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Publicity Guadalajara, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Guadalajara, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Israel Hebrew and Tel Aviv Breakdown of Costs, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Israel Breakdown of Costs, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Israel Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Israel Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Israel Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Israel Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Israel Committee, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Israel Consortium for SUNY Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - FSLP Israel, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Student Informational Brochure for Israel, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Director (applications for) Israel, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Israel Directors Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Israel Directors Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Israel Directors Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Israel Directors Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Evaluation Questionnaire Israel - Tel Aviv, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Israel Evaluations, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Evaluation Questionnaire Israel - Hebrew University, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Israel Financial Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Israel Financial Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Israel, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Israel Info, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Israel Info Sent to Students, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Israel Info Sent to Students, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Israel Interim Program, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Israel Oneonta Students, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Israel Oneonta, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Israel Orientation, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Israel Orientation, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Israel General Correspondence, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Israel Participants, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Israel Participants, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Israel Participants Hebrew University, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Alexandria- Tel Aviv Program, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Israel Participants Hebrew University, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Israel Participants Tel-Aviv, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Israel Participants Hebrew University, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Israel Participants Tel-Aviv, 1975-19796 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Israel Participants Tel-Aviv, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Israel Participants HAIFA, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Participants HAIFA, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Israel Participants Hebrew University, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Israel Participants Tel-Aviv, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Israel Programs, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Israel Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Israel Programs, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Israel Programs, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Israel Programs, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - President Director Israel, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Israel Task Force, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Israel Task Force, 1971-1976 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Israel Task Force, 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Israel Underground Program, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Israel TESL, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Israel Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Israel Program Adviser, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Israel Program Orientation Packet, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Israel Participants, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Israel Participants University of Halfa, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Israel Participants University Hebrew University, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Israel Participants University Hebrew University, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Israel Programs, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Madrid Program Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - General Information Madrid Program, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Madrid Breakdown of Costs, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Madrid Costs, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Madrid Breakdown of Costs, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Madrid Budget, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Madrid Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Madrid Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Madrid Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Madrid Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Madrid Directors Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Madrid Directors Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Madrid Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Madrid Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Madrid Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Madrid Course Descriptions, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Madrid Directors Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Madrid Directors Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Madrid Directors Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Madrid Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Madrid Costs Spring, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Madrid Course Descriptions, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Madrid Course Descriptions, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Course Listings Madrid, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Madrid Course Listings, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Madrid Course Descriptions, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Madrid Directors Financial, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Madrid Participants, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Madrid Evaluations Spring, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Madrid Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Madrid Evaluations, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Madrid Evaluations, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Evaluation Questionnaire Madrid, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Madrid Financial Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Madrid Financial Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Madrid Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Madrid Evaluations, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Madrid Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Madrid Program Information, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Madrid Info, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Madrid Info Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Madrid Info, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Madrid, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Madrid, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Madrid Participants, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Madrid Participants, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Madrid Participants, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Madrid Participants, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Madrid Participants, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Madrid Participants, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Madrid Program, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Madrid Program, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - General Information Madrid Program, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Madrid Program, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Madrid Program, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Madrid Program, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Madrid Program, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Madrid Program, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Madrid Program, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Madrid Program, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Printing - Madrid, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Program Advisor, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Soviet/SUNY Program Committee, 1974-1978 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Madrid Program Adviser, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Madrid Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Madrid Program, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Madrid Courses Description, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Madrid Participants, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Madrid, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Madrid, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Nanyang Brochure, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Nanyang Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Nanyang Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Nanyang Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Nanyang Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Nanyang Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Nanyang Committee, 1967-1975 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Nanyang Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Nanyang Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Nanyang Directors Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Nanyang Directors Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Nanyang Directors Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Nanyang Directors Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Nanyang Directors Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Nanyang Directors Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Evaluations Nanyang, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Evaluations Nanyang, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Evaluations Nanyang, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Nanyang Exchange Professor, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Nanyang Exchange Professor, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Nanyang Financial Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Nanyang Flight, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Nanyang Info, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Nanyang Info, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Lists Nanyang, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Nanyang Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Nanyang Hilo Orientation, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Nanyang Participants, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Nanyang Participants, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Nanyang Participants, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Nanyang Participants, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Nanyang Programs, 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Nanyang Participants, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Nanyang Participants, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Nanyang University Program, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Nanyang Program Information [1 of 2], 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Nanyang Program Information [2 of 2], 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Nanyang Program, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Nanyang Program, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Nanyang Program, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Nanyang Program, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Nanyang Program, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Nanyang Withdrawals, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Nice Administration, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Application for Nice, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Admin Asst., 1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Nice Birth Certification, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Nice Brochure, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Binghamton Nice, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Nice Breakdown of Costs, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Nice Brochures, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Nice Budget, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Nice Breakdown of Costs, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Nice Budget, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Buffalo Nice, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Nice Centre Socio-Pedagogique, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Nice Clippings, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Materials Distributed to Nice Advisory Committee, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Nice Committee, 1973-1979 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Nice Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - SUNYA Nice Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Advisory Nice Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - SUNYA Nice Committee, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Advisory Nice Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Nice Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Nice Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Nice Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Nice Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Nice Committee, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Advisory Nice Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Nice Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Alexander Fischler Nice Correspondence, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Oscar Haac Nice Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Ludovit Linczenyl Nice Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Nice Director Fred More, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Fred More - Nice, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Nice Director Sandy Petrey, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Nice Directors Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Nice Director, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Nice Directors Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Nice Directors Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Nice Directors Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Nice Directors Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Nice Directors Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Nice Evaluations, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Nice Evaluations, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Nice Evaluations, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Nice Evaluations, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Nice Evaluations, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Nice Evaluations, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Nice Finances, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Nice Directors Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Nice Financial, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Nice Financing, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Evaluation Questionnaires Nice France, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Nice Director Financial, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Nice Financial Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Nice Financial Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Nice Forms, 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Nice Student Forms, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Nice Program Forms, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Nice Forms, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Nice General, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Letterbook - Charles W. Colman, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Nice Graduate Students, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Universiti de Nice, Undated (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Nice House, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Nice Info Letters, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Nice Information, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Nice Info, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Nice Info Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Nice Info, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Marc Alexandre Substitute Europeer, 1968-1971 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Letters to Nice Participants, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Nice Lists, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Nice Lists, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Nice Logistics, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Nice, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Nice, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Nice, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Nice, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Nice Orientation, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Nice Orientation, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Nice Orientation, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Nice Orientation, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Nice Orientation, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Nice Participants, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Nice Participants, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Nice Participants, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Nice Participants, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Nice Participants, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Nice Participants, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Nice Participants, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Nice Planning File, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Planning Program, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Nice Planning, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Presession - Nice Frazee, Ronald, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Nice Pre-session, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Nice Pre-session, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Nice Pre-session, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Nice Pre-session, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Nice Visas, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Nice Pre-session, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Nice Pre-session, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Nice Pre-session, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Nice Pre-session, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Nice Program Plans, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Nice Program, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Nice Program, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Program Proposal Format Nice, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 41)